* Apps

* Help

Browsec Privacy Policy
======================

December 5, 2023

This privacy policy sets forth how Browsec Inc collects and processes personal information from any user of our services, as well as our use and disclosure of such information.

When you use our service, you agree to let us process your information as we describe in this Privacy Policy statement.

1. Collection of personal information
    ----------------------------------
    
    1. ### Personal information
        
        «Personal information» means any information that identifies you, this includes information provided by you when using our services.
        
    2. ### Cookies
        
        When you visit browsec.com website, we may store one or more cookies — a small text string — on your computer. These cookies can be persistent, that is, they may remain after you close your browser window. Please refer to your browser’s «Help» for information on removing cookies.
        
    3. ### Account information
        
        When you create your Browsec account, we provide you with an anonymous Account ID . You may also link additional information to your account, such as your e-mail address.
        
        We also store brief information about your Browsec subscriptions as data associated with your account.
        
        To remove your account from our system, please send us an account deletion request using this link [contact us](https://browsec.com/en/contact_us). What will happen after your request to delete your Browsec account:
        
        * Email address record and its association with internal Account ID from Browsec system will be permanently deleted.
        * All active subscriptions associated with your account will be cancelled. Important: we will cancel only the subscriptions made via our website and via Google Play. App Store subscription cancellation, however, is not available to us. You will need to cancel such a subscription by yourself.
        * All custom settings in Browsec apps made under the account will be lost permanently.
        * You will be automatically logged out on all your devices.
        
        The following data will be kept in our system, however totally anonymous and not related to your email address:
        
        * Activity records of the device as part of operational data set we use to monitor and improve our service performance.
        * Records of consents given under this account.
        
    4. ### Operational data
        
        To ensure the continuous delivery of our Services, we have to automatically record some information from your web browser additional/or client software. The information does not identify the User personally. Browsec uses such information in the aggregate for various purposes, including the monitoring of the service.
        
2. Use of Personal Information
    ---------------------------
    
    1. ### Use
        
        Browsec may use automatically-collected information in the aggregate for the purpose of monitoring, research or analysis. The information is collected only when the Browsec service is currently active.
        
    2. ### Disclosure
        
        Browsec does not disclose your Personal information unless it is required by the legal law enforcement requests.
        
3. Changes to this Privacy Policy
    ------------------------------
    
    We may need to update the Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Service after the effective date of such changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes. The effective date will be reflected in the «last modified» notice above.
    
4. Contact information
    -------------------
    
    If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@browsec.com](mailto:support@browsec.com).

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Platforms<br><br>* [VPN for Chrome](https://browsec.com/en/chrome-vpn)<br>* [VPN for Firefox](https://browsec.com/en/firefox-vpn)<br>* [VPN for iOS](https://browsec.com/en/ios-vpn)<br>* [VPN for Android](https://browsec.com/en/android-vpn)<br>* [VPN for Windows](https://browsec.com/en/windows-vpn)<br>* [VPN for Mac OS](https://browsec.com/en/vpn-mac)<br><br>Prices<br><br>* [Plans and pricing](https://browsec.com/en/orders/new?plan_id=annual)<br>* [Premium](https://browsec.com/en/plans)<br><br>Why use a VPN<br><br>* [What is my IP](https://browsec.com/en/what-is-my-ip)<br>* [What is a VPN](https://browsec.com/en/what-is-a-vpn)<br>* [Free VPN](https://browsec.com/en/free-vpn)<br>* [Check your VPN](https://browsec.com/en/vpn-check)<br>* [Is your phone hacked](https://browsec.com/en/how-to-tell-if-your-phone-is-hacked)<br><br>Information<br><br>* [Contact us](https://browsec.com/en/contact_us)<br>* [FAQ](https://browsec.com/en/faq)<br>* [Help Center](https://browsec.zendesk.com/hc/en-us?utm_source=website&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=footer)<br>* [Our Telegram channel](https://t.me/BrowsecVPNofficial/) | Downloads<br><br>[Available in the Chrome Web Store](https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/browsec-vpn-free-vpn-for/omghfjlpggmjjaagoclmmobgdodcjboh)<br><br>[Get it on Google Play](https://browsec.page.link/app)<br><br>[Download on the AppStore](https://apps.apple.com/us/app/browsec-vpn-fast-ads-free/id978583103) |
| Products<br><br>[DNS Leaks](https://browsec.com/en/features/dns-leak) [F1 Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/f1) [Football / Soccer Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/football) [Free Disney Plus VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/disney) [Free Gaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/gaming) [Free Hulu VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/hulu) [Free Netflix VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/netflix) [Free Reddit VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/reddit) [Free Sports Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/sport) [Free Telegram VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/telegram) [Free Twitter VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/twitter) [IPL Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/ipl) [MLB Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/mlb) [MMA Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/mma) [Mobile Legends Free VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/mobile-legends) [MotoGP Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/motogp) [NBA Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/nba) [NFL Streaming VPN](https://browsec.com/en/features/nfl) [VPN for YouTube](https://browsec.com/en/features/youtube) |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| [VPN Locations](https://browsec.com/en/locations/all)<br><br>[Australia](https://browsec.com/en/locations/australia)[Austria](https://browsec.com/en/locations/austria)[Belgium](https://browsec.com/en/locations/belgium)[Brazil](https://browsec.com/en/locations/brazil)[Bulgaria](https://browsec.com/en/locations/bulgaria)[Canada](https://browsec.com/en/locations/canada)[Chile](https://browsec.com/en/locations/chile)[Croatia](https://browsec.com/en/locations/croatia)[Cyprus](https://browsec.com/en/locations/cyprus)[Czech Republic](https://browsec.com/en/locations/czech-republic)[Denmark](https://browsec.com/en/locations/denmark)[Finland](https://browsec.com/en/locations/finland)[France](https://browsec.com/en/locations/france)[Germany](https://browsec.com/en/locations/germany)[Greece](https://browsec.com/en/locations/greece)[Hong Kong](https://browsec.com/en/locations/hong-kong)[Hungary](https://browsec.com/en/locations/hungary)[Iceland](https://browsec.com/en/locations/iceland)[India](https://browsec.com/en/locations/india)[Ireland](https://browsec.com/en/locations/ireland)[Israel](https://browsec.com/en/locations/israel)[Italy](https://browsec.com/en/locations/italy)[Japan](https://browsec.com/en/locations/japan)[Latvia](https://browsec.com/en/locations/latvia)[Lithuania](https://browsec.com/en/locations/lithuania)[Luxembourg](https://browsec.com/en/locations/luxembourg)[Mexico](https://browsec.com/en/locations/mexico)[Netherlands](https://browsec.com/en/locations/netherlands)[New Zealand](https://browsec.com/en/locations/new-zealand)[Norway](https://browsec.com/en/locations/norway)[Poland](https://browsec.com/en/locations/poland)[Romania](https://browsec.com/en/locations/romania)[Russia](https://browsec.com/en/locations/russia)[Serbia](https://browsec.com/en/locations/serbia)[Singapore](https://browsec.com/en/locations/singapore)[Slovenia](https://browsec.com/en/locations/slovenia)[South Africa](https://browsec.com/en/locations/south-africa)[South Korea](https://browsec.com/en/locations/south-korea)[Spain](https://browsec.com/en/locations/spain)[Sweden](https://browsec.com/en/locations/sweden)[Switzerland](https://browsec.com/en/locations/switzerland)[Turkey](https://browsec.com/en/locations/turkey)[Ukraine](https://browsec.com/en/locations/ukraine)[United Kingdom](https://browsec.com/en/locations/united-kingdom)[United States](https://browsec.com/en/locations/us)[United States (West)](https://browsec.com/en/locations/us-west) |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| Browsec<br><br>© 2012 — 2024 Browsec Inc<br><br>[Contact us](https://browsec.com/en/contact_us)<br><br>[Privacy policy](https://browsec.com/en/privacypolicy)<br><br>[Terms of service](https://browsec.com/en/terms_of_service) |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
